Kniffin, Kevin Collection of University of Wisconsin System Collective Bargaining Files 6340
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Publications. 1938-2011 (Box 3)
  - UFAS. Flyers 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 8: United Faculty & Academic Staff, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 9: Legislative Initiative, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: January
    - Item 10: Did You Know?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 11: Will you take a moment to help us?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 12: Collective Bargaining - Next Steps, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 13: Collective Bargaining - Next Steps, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 14: Collective Bargaining - Next Steps, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 15: Collective Bargaining - Next Steps, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 16: Crisis in Higher Education Conference, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: Saturday, April 5
    - Item 17: Legislative Initiative, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 18: Health Insurance Costs Demonstrate Need for Fairness and Rights, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 19: Your $700 Missing Paycheck, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 20: UW Faculty deserve a real voice, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Author: Tim Shiell
      Notes: January 29
    - Item 21: Research Experiment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 22: UFAS Caucus Letter, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Author: Kirkland, Becky; Linder, Jessica; Ross, Dan
      Notes: May 12
    - Item 23: Defend our Healthcare, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 24: Fact Sheet on UW System Healthcare and Pay Raise Proposals, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 25: A Veto Message That Makes Us Wonder, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 26: Benefits of TAUWP Membership, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 27: Administrations FAILS UW Academic Staff and Faculty, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 28: COPE Reception, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 29: Delegate Strength, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: 2004 AFT-Wisconsin Convention
    - Item 30: Health Care Forum, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: August 27
    - Item 31: Faculty and Academic Staff, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 32: Getting Started with UFAS, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 33: Faculty and Academic Stuff, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 34: Know Your Rights!!!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 35: Teaching Unions, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: Saturday, April 3
    - Item 36: Profs Inc., Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 37: TAUWP, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - UFAS. News 2003-2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: UFAS News, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Vol. 4, No. 5, June
    - Item 2: UFAS News, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Vol. 4, No. 5 June
    - Item 3: UFAS News, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Vol. 3, No. 7, April
    - Item 4: Performance Review and Job Security, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 5: Wisconsinites support tax shifts to fund education, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Vol. 3, Issue 1, September
    - Item 6: UFAS News, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: July
    - Item 7: UFAS e-news, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Sunday, February 19
    - Item 8: e-news, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Notes: Vol. 2, No. 6, February
  - WEAC/WFT. Update for WEAC/WFT Leaders 1994, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Update for WEAC/WFT leaders, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Notes: No. 20, March 7
  - Wisconsin State. Governor's Commission on University of Wisconsin System Compensation 1992, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: 1992 Report of the Governor's Commission on University of Wisconsin System Compensation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Wisconsin State Association of Wisconsin State College Faculties' Conference Booklets 1938-1960 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Biennial Conference, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 29 and 30
    - Item 2: Biennial Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 18 and 19
    - Item 3: Biennial Conference, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 30 - May 1
    - Item 4: Biennial Conference, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 25-26
    - Item 5: Biennial Conference, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 28-29
    - Item 6: Eau Claire Convention Map Guide, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Item 7: Conference, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: March 20 and 21
    - Item 8: Conference, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Notes: April 13 and 14
  - Collective Bargaining Poster, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: TAUWP, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Notes: Cardboard Poster